Well, so I would like to.
I bet you would like to, but that doesn't mean you're going to. Are you?
No, no, no. What I'm saying to you is the Congress has statutes on seditious conspiracy,
on insurrection, on impeding federal law enforcement.
The domestic terrorism statute in Congress obviously needs to be strengthened for domestic terrorism in Congress.
We have foreign terrorism charges.
We have an entire patchwork of federal laws.
To the extent that there are charges that apply, we will charge them in every single case.
You have impeding law enforcement. You have seditious conspiracy.
You have a conspiracy to the private rights.
You have assault against law enforcement officers.
But all of this meets the hallmark textbook definitions of domestic terrorism.
I just want, Boris, I just want you just for a moment to step back and think about what we're talking about here.
We, President Trump ran and won a campaign on turning back the border invasion.
You've said that several times, Stephen.
We have a limited amount of time, so let me ask you.
Let me ask you about the governor of Illinois.
Peter is going to be a no-go zone for ICE.
How is that not insurrection?
Stephen, Stephen, we're set to hear from J.B. Pritzker in just moments.
He says that you're attempting to inflame tensions and create a war zone.
He also says that you are profiling, that you're targeting black and brown people,
even those who turn out to be here legally.
What's your response?
Thank you.